I think I like being up early.
我想我喜欢早起.
That's a little more relaxed.
这样更放松一些.
I have to be here by 5 on weekdays and 4:30 on Sunday,
我必须工作日5点到这, 周日4:30到,
but I, I work four days a week here.
但我一周工作4天.
I kind of stagger it.
我会把工作日错开.
Sometimes you lose some sleep but you have to do what you have to do to make a living.
有时你会丢掉一些睡眠, 但你需要做你需要做的事情为了谋生.
I really don't mind coming in early.
我并不介意早点来.
I, you know, I get in, I get a place to park,
我,you know,我到了之后,找个地方停车,
I come down, I get some stuff done and,
然后下来做点什么事情,
you know, I like walking down the street in the morning.
you know,我喜欢早晨在街上漫步.
It's kind of like my cup of coffee to get going.
这样做有点像开始工作前先喝杯咖啡.
Well, I don't have much of a social life right now.
Well,我现在社交活动不多.
I'm just working all the time.
所有时间都是在工作.
I don't go out a lot at night.
我晚上不太出门.
I, you know, I've got a wife and tow kids,
我,you know,我有妻子和两个孩子,
so I spend most of the time with them,
所以我大部分时间和他们在一起,
and I stay up not overly late.
晚上也不过度熬夜.
But it does change, you know, I'm a little tired,
情况不一样了,you know,我有点累,
come, you know, 10 o'clock at night.
一到晚上10点钟.
I'm, you know, I don't have a lot of energy left.
我就,you know,我就精力不足了.
I'm here from midnight till 8 in the morning,
我从半夜到早上8点一直在这里,
er, four nights a week; Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday,
er,一周4个晚上:周五,周六,周日,周一,
and it's a great deal of fun
这样很有意思,
because it also gives me four daytimes off each week.
因为这样我一周可以有4个白天休息.
The nighttime customers are, for the most part,
晚间的顾客,大部分,
a little drunk, definitely very hungry,
有点醉,肯定非常饿,
they've spent a lot of money,
他们花了许多钱,
they're on their way home,
正在回家的路上,
they're sleepy, they're tired,
他们又累又困,
they want food with no effort as quickly as humanly possible.
他们想毫不费力地、尽可能快地吃到东西.
The morning people tend to,
早起的人趋向于,
they want some nice peace and quiet,
他们喜欢宁静,
maybe just get started for the day.
也许是为新的一天做准备.
They're waking up,
他们正在逐渐清醒过来,
they don't want to get blasted
他们不想被惊醒,
and they don't want to walk straight into work,
也不想径直去上班,
so they come in, they settle down,
所以他们来到这里,坐下来,
they have a cup of coffee,
喝杯咖啡,
they talk about last night's news
谈谈前一晚的新闻,
and then they move on.
然后离开.